{
    "id": "b413dc4b5d0643dcb4358c0d4b245f26",
    "title": "Phrasal verbs with take exercise",
    "exercises": [
        {
            "id": "de816a35f2dc4413aabde1aef918d886",
            "title": "Phrasal Verbs With Take",
            "questions": [
                {
                    "question": "She takes ………………… her grandmother.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "in",
                        "off",
                        "after"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "They assaulted the watchmen and took many precious paintings ………………… .",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "off",
                        "down",
                        "away"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "These shoes don’t fit. I am going to take them ………………… .. to the store.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "away",
                        "back",
                        "off"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "Don’t take him ………………….. an idiot.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "in",
                        "for",
                        "off"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "The dress was loose for me so I took it to the tailor and got it taken …………………",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "out",
                        "in",
                        "off"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "Please take your shoes ………………… .. before entering the temple.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "away",
                        "down",
                        "off"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "How are you going to meet the deadlines if you take ………………… . too many projects?",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "in",
                        "on",
                        "out"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "If you love Susie why don’t you take her ………………… on a date?",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "in",
                        "up",
                        "out"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "He took ………………… farming after retirement.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "in",
                        "out",
                        "up"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "We will take this issue ………………… . when we meet next week.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "up",
                        "on",
                        "over"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                }
            ]
        }
    ]
}